[{"answer": "Skip, It's me! I'm not some quote piece of ass unquote", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You can't ban me from the ballpark 'cause Daddy donated the scoreboard and if you banned me he might take the scoreboard away", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Got time for another quickie", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "But we got three minutes", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I got lured", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "\"I didn't get lured and I will take responsibility for my action", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You didn't get", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "That's better.  Got the radar ready", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm my friend", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't dance", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend. Wanta dance", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't trust a man who don't dance. It ain't natural", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Shut up", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It's a damn easy thing to play with", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Wait, Crash", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm not interested yet", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You mean Nuke. You said", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You said", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How come you don't like me", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What do I got", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "\"Na", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You're through with one night stands?! What do you want", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Sorry. You look great. I'm totally exhausted", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Catch", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "This in ridiculous. I'm a pro", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Which nostril am I breathing through", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm yours", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Breathing through your pingala always works, honey", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Don't bump me", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Did you call me a cocksucker", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It was a cocksucking call", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No! I said It was a coc", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You missed the tag", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I didn't spit on you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You're close, Crash, you want me to run you? I'll run you", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Try it! Go ahead. Call me a cocksucker", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You will.  Look, Nuke", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " No. Fear and arrogance, you, hayseed, not ignorance", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I think I'm ready for the Show", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Don't worry", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I'm quitting too. Boys, not baseball", "docId": "Bull-Durham.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "that place, that place? Where all the witches were", "qsentId": 42}]